Guide to the DoubleTake Records, 1908-1999, bulk 1994-1999 RL.00321
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession (2010-0081): DoubleTake Records, 1993-1998, 281241; 41 boxes
  - Goin, 282027 (Box 13)
  - Goldberg, Jim, 282026 (Box 13)
  - Goldman, Jonathan, 282025 (Box 13)
  - Goldstein, Rick, 282024 (Box 13)
  - Goldstein/Drawings, 282023 (Box 13)
  - Goldworm, Irving, 282022 (Box 13)
  - Goodman, John, 282021 (Box 13)
  - Goodman, Mark, 282020 (Box 13)
  - Goldblatt, David, 282019 (Box 13)
  - Gonzalez, Tony, 282018 (Box 13)
  - Gordon, Richard, 282017 (Box 13)
  - Gottfried, Arlene, 282016 (Box 13)
  - Gowin, Elijah, 282015 (Box 13)
  - Gowin, Emmet, 282014 (Box 13)
  - Graffeo, Karen, 282013 (Box 13)
  - Graham, David, 282012 (Box 13)
  - Graham, Ian, 282011 (Box 13)
  - Graves, Ken and Eva Lipman, 282010 (Box 13)
  - Graves, Kristin, 282009 (Box 14)
  - Grazda, Ed, 282008 (Box 14)
  - Greenberg, Mark, 282007 (Box 14)
  - Greenberg, Stanley, 282006 (Box 14)
  - Greenfield, Lauren, 282005 (Box 14)
  - Greiner, William, 282004 (Box 14)
  - Grigsby, Bryan, 282003 (Box 14)
  - Grillo, Gina, 282002 (Box 14)
  - Grimes, Tom, 282001 (Box 14)
  - Grosse, Eric, 282000 (Box 14)
  - Grossman, Joel, 281999 (Box 14)
  - Groth, Bonnie Lee, 281998 (Box 14)
  - Gruyaert, 281997 (Box 14)
  - Guardans, Xavier, 281996 (Box 14)
  - Guarnaccia, Steven, 281995 (Box 14)
  - Gubbins, William, 281994 (Box 14)
  - Gudmundson, Wayne, 281993 (Box 14)
  - Gumpert, Robert, 281992 (Box 14)
  - Hackett, Thomas, 281991 (Box 14)
  - Hair, Jim, 281990 (Box 14)
  - Hales, Kevin, 281989 (Box 14)
  - Hall, John, 281988 (Box 14)
  - Halverson, Karen, 281987 (Box 14)
  - Hamilton, Alisa, 281986 (Box 14)
  - Hanlon, David, 281985 (Box 14)
  - Hanson, David, 281984 (Box 14)
  - Hansson, Sven-Erik, 281983 (Box 14)
  - Harding, John, 281982 (Box 14)
  - Hardy, Angela, 281981 (Box 14)
  - Harbutt, Charlie, 281980 (Box 14)
  - Harkness, Chris, 281979 (Box 14)
  - Harnett, Matt (2 folders), 281978 (Box 14)
  - Harney, Tom, 281977 (Box 14)
  - Harrington, Christopher, 281976 (Box 14)
  - Harris, James W., 281975 (Box 14)
  - Hart, Russell, 281974 (Box 14)
  - Hartman, Eric, 281973 (Box 14)
  - Hatch, Dede, 281972 (Box 14)
  - Hauge-Giovanzana, Teresa, 281971 (Box 14)
  - Haven, Mark, 281970 (Box 14)
  - Hawthorn, Ann Parks, 281969 (Box 14)
  - Hayashi, Masumi, 281968 (Box 15)
  - Hayward, Barbara, 281967 (Box 15)
  - Heath, Bonnie, 281966 (Box 15)
  - Heberlein, David, 281965 (Box 15)
  - Heebner, Mary, 281964 (Box 15)
  - Hendler, 281963 (Box 15)
  - De Henning, Anne, 281962 (Box 15)
  - Herman, Todd, 281961 (Box 15)
  - Hernandez, Anthony, 281960 (Box 15)
  - Hernandez, Cristina and Richard Koci, 281959 (Box 15)
  - Hess, Bill, 281958 (Box 15)
  - Hesse and McNeil, 281957 (Box 15)
  - Heykants, Kristine, 281956 (Box 15)
  - Heyman, Abbey, 281955 (Box 15)
  - Hido, Todd, 281954 (Box 15)
  - Higgins, Deck, 281953 (Box 15)
  - Hill, Douglas, 281952 (Box 15)
  - Hintlian, Michael J., 281951 (Box 15)
  - Hirshan, Karen, 281950 (Box 15)
  - Hirshfeld, Max, 281949 (Box 15)
  - Hodges, John, 281948 (Box 15)
  - Hoggson, Julia Beck, 281947 (Box 15)
  - Holbrooke, A., 281946 (Box 15)
  - Holdt, Jacob, 281945 (Box 15)
  - Holiday Cards (Winter 1996), 281944 (Box 15)
  - Hollyman, Stephenie, 281943 (Box 15)
  - Hope Archive 9, 281942 (Box 15)
  - Hornbeck, Carol, 281941 (Box 15)
  - Hornstein, Henry, 281940 (Box 15)
  - Horowitz, Lenore, 281939 (Box 15)
  - Hoskins, Sarah, 281938 (Box 15)
  - Hoshino, Marvin, 281937 (Box 15)
  - Howard, Billy, 281936 (Box 16)
  - Howe, Joel, 281935 (Box 16)
  - Hoyer, Andrea C., 281934 (Box 16)
  - Hubbard, Tom, 281933 (Box 16)
  - Hubber, Laura, 281932 (Box 16)
  - Huddleston, John (2 folders), 281931 (Box 16)
  - Huff, Linda, 281930 (Box 16)
  - Hughes, Jon C., 281929 (Box 16)
  - Hujar, Peter, 281928 (Box 16)
  - Hulf, T.K., 281927 (Box 16)
  - Humble, John, 281926 (Box 16)
  - Hunt, Chad, 281925 (Box 16)
  - Hurn, David, 281924 (Box 16)
  - Hurst, Richard, 281923 (Box 16)
  - Huskey, Brian, 281922 (Box 16)
  - Iacono, Kim, 281921 (Box 16)
  - Imes, Birney, 281920 (Box 16)
  - Isaacs-Rafson, Hillary, 281919 (Box 16)
  - Ito, Hiroyuki, 281918 (Box 16)
  - Izu, Kenro, 281917 (Box 16)
  - Jacobs, Hortense, 281916 (Box 16)
  - Jacobsen, Colin, 281915 (Box 16)
  - Jacobson, Jeff, 281914 (Box 16)
  - Jacobson-Hardy, Michael, 281913 (Box 17)
  - Jarman, Janet, 281912 (Box 17)
  - J.B. Pictures Ltd., 281911 (Box 17)
  - Jenkins, Sherman, 281910 (Box 17)
  - Jenshel, Len, 281909 (Box 17)
  - Jenz, Tom, 281908 (Box 17)
  - Johnson, Dion, 281907 (Box 17)
  - Johnson, Lynn, 281906 (Box 17)
  - Johnson, Michael, 281905 (Box 17)
  - Jones, Sherry, 281904 (Box 17)
  - Jonkmans, Bernd, 281903 (Box 17)
  - Jordan, Bruce, 281902 (Box 17)
  - Joseph, Eddy, 281901 (Box 17)
  - Jude, Ron, 281900 (Box 17)
  - Kahn, Steve, 281899 (Box 17)
  - Kaida, Tamarra, 281898 (Box 17)
  - Kalisher, Simpson, 281897 (Box 17)
  - Kamikura, Yoshiko, 281896 (Box 17)
  - Kamoinge, 281895 (Box 17)
  - Kanemura, Osamu, 281894 (Box 17)
  - Kang, Hee Jim, 281893 (Box 17)
  - Kaplan, Kevin, 281892 (Box 17)
  - Kapuscinski, Sylvia, 281891 (Box 17)
  - Kariotakis, Ana, 281890 (Box 17)
  - Karagozian, Ken, 281889 (Box 17)
  - Kashi, Ed, 281888 (Box 17)
  - Kasterine, Dmitri, 281887 (Box 17)
  - Katchian, Sonia, 281886 (Box 17)
  - Kazimierski, Daniel, 281885 (Box 17)
  - Keim, Denise, 281884 (Box 17)
  - Keithan, Mary, 281883 (Box 17)
  - Keller, Benita, 281882 (Box 17)
  - Kennard, John, 281881 (Box 17)
  - Kelliher, Patricia, 281880 (Box 17)
  - Kendrick, Ruth, 281879 (Box 17)
  - Kenney, Marcus, 281878 (Box 17)
  - Kensington, Victoria, 281877 (Box 17)
  - Kereszi, Lisa, 281876 (Box 17)
  - Kernan, Sean, 281875 (Box 17)
  - Kertesz, Andre, 281874 (Box 17)
  - Kessler, Brad, 281873 (Box 17)
  - Kim, Helen, 281872 (Box 17)
  - Kimmerling, George, 281871 (Box 17)
  - Kingston, Rodger, 281870 (Box 17)
  - Kleckner, Susan, 281869 (Box 18)
  - Kleinhenz, Laura, 281868 (Box 18)
  - Kleitsch, Chad, 281867 (Box 18)
  - Klett, Mark, 281866 (Box 18)
  - Klich, Kent, 281865 (Box 18)
  - Klipper, Stuart, 281864 (Box 18)
  - Klugman, Karen, 281863 (Box 18)
  - Koch, Ferne, 281862 (Box 18)
  - Koga, Mary, 281861 (Box 18)
  - Konic, Stephanie, 281860 (Box 18)
  - Kosarich, Rick, 281859 (Box 18)
  - Koster, Axel, 281858 (Box 18)
  - Kotchen, Robert, 281857 (Box 18)
  - Kral, Jan, 281856 (Box 18)
  - Kranz, Nancy, 281855 (Box 18)
  - Kratochvil, Antonin (2 folders), 281854 (Box 18)
  - Kuhn, Penny, 281853 (Box 18)
  - Kunhardt, Amelia (Amy), 281852 (Box 18)
  - Kuo, Alex, 281851 (Box 18)
  - Kurspahic, Kemal, 281850 (Box 18)
  - Kwiatkowska, Michelle, 281849 (Box 18)
  - Ladd, Jeff, 281848 (Box 18)
  - Landy, Neal, 281847 (Box 18)
  - Lane, Joni, 281846 (Box 18)
  - Lang, Mary Stuart, 281845 (Box 18)
  - Lang, Michael, 281844 (Box 18)
  - Lange, Dorothea, 281843 (Box 18)
  - Langer, Jason, 281842 (Box 18)
  - Lantos, Lauren, 281841 (Box 18)
  - Larsen, Flynn, 281840 (Box 18)
  - Larson, Krisitine, 281839 (Box 18)
  - Lassalle, Sebastian, 281838 (Box 18)
  - Laughlin, Ray, 281837 (Box 18)
  - Lavigne, Jill, 281836 (Box 18)
  - Lawrence, John, 281835 (Box 18)
  - Layton, Elizabeth, 281834 (Box 18)
  - Le, An-My, 281833 (Box 18)
  - Le, Thinh, 281832 (Box 18)
  - Leaken, Kitty, 281831 (Box 18)
  - Ledford, Stretch, 281830 (Box 18)
  - Ledger, Bill, 281829 (Box 18)
  - Ledochowski, Chris, 281828 (Box 18)
  - Lee, Bud, 281827 (Box 18)
  - Lee, Jocelyn, 281826 (Box 18)
  - Lee, Lance, 281825 (Box 19)
  - Lee, Chang, 281824 (Box 19)
  - Lee, Susan, 281823 (Box 19)
  - Lee, Ron, 281822 (Box 19)
  - Leebrick, Gil, 281821 (Box 19)
  - Lehman, Steve, 281820 (Box 19)
  - Lehr, John, 281819 (Box 19)
  - Leiter, Saul, 281818 (Box 19)
  - Lekberg, Andrea, 281817 (Box 19)
  - Lemonick, Eileen Hohmuth, 281816 (Box 19)
  - Leonard, Joanne, 281815 (Box 19)
  - Leong, Mark, 281814 (Box 19)
  - Lepkoff, Rebecca, 281813 (Box 19)
  - Lerager, James, 281812 (Box 19)
  - Leskovak, Diana, 281811 (Box 19)
  - Lester, Alvin, 281810 (Box 19)
  - Lesy, M./Detroit Publishing Co., 281809 (Box 19)
  - Lewis, Payne, 281808 (Box 19)
  - Levitt - Mexico (8 folders), 281807 (Box 19)
  - Letinsky, Laura, 281806 (Box 20)
  - Letourneau, John, 281805 (Box 20)
  - Levenstein, Matvey, 281804 (Box 20)
  - Levin, Meryl (2 folders), 281803 (Box 20)
  - Levin, Mimi, 281802 (Box 20)
  - Levin, Wayne (2 folders), 281801 (Box 20)
  - Levine, Anna, 281800 (Box 20)
  - Levine, Ron, 281799 (Box 20)
  - Levins, Mike, 281798 (Box 20)
  - Levinthal, David, 281797 (Box 20)
  - Levthold, Catherine, 281796 (Box 20)
  - Levy, Alyson, 281795 (Box 20)
  - Levy, Builder, 281794 (Box 20)
  - Levy, Janice, 281793 (Box 20)
  - Levy, Rob, 281792 (Box 20)
  - Lewis, Michael, 281791 (Box 20)
  - Lichtenstein, Alex, 281790 (Box 20)
  - Liebling, Jerome, 281789 (Box 20)
  - Liftin, Joan, 281788 (Box 20)
  - Light, Ken, 281787 (Box 20)
  - Lindman, Peter, 281786 (Box 20)
  - Linnemeier-Marshall, Lynn, 281785 (Box 20)
  - Lipper, Susan, 281784 (Box 20)
  - Lippman, Susan, 281783 (Box 20)
  - Llerena, Roberto, 281782 (Box 20)
  - Locke, Kris, 281781 (Box 20)
  - Loewenberg, Ina, 281780 (Box 20)
  - Loengard, John, 281779 (Box 20)
  - Lomax, Alan, 281778 (Box 20)
  - Lorusso, Nicola, 281777 (Box 20)
  - Lowe, Jeffrey, 281776 (Box 20)
  - Lozowick, Louis, 281775 (Box 21)
  - Luckett, James, 281774 (Box 21)
  - Lueders-Booth, John, 281773 (Box 21)
  - Luster, Debbie, 281772 (Box 21)
  - Lutter, Vera, 281771 (Box 21)
  - Lutzen, Andre, 281770 (Box 21)
  - Lynch, David, 281769 (Box 21)
  - Lynnworth, Jill, 281768 (Box 21)
  - Lynton, Holly, 281767 (Box 21)
  - Lyon, Danny (3 folders), 281766 (Box 21)
  - Lyons, Robert, 281765 (Box 21)
  - MacDougall, Mal, 281764 (Box 21)
  - MacNeil, Wendy Snyder, 281763 (Box 21)
  - MacWeeney, Alan, 281762 (Box 21)
  - Maher, Mike, 281761 (Box 21)
  - Maisel, David, 281760 (Box 21)
  - Manheimer, Kara, 281759 (Box 21)
  - Manly, Roger, 281758 (Box 21)
  - Mann, Robert, 281757 (Box 21)
  - Mann, Sally, 281756 (Box 21)
  - Marasco, Rose, 281755 (Box 21)
  - Marden, Malerie, 281754 (Box 21)
  - Marin, Richard, 281753 (Box 21)
  - Marin, Roger, 281752 (Box 21)
  - Mariner's Museum, 281751 (Box 22)
  - Marino, Carol, 281750 (Box 22)
  - Mark, Mary Ellen, 281749 (Box 22)
  - Maroukian, Francine, 281748 (Box 22)
  - Marshall, Karen, 281747 (Box 22)
  - Marshall, Kerry, 281746 (Box 22)
  - Martin, Carl, 281745 (Box 22)
  - Mason, Charles, 281744 (Box 22)
  - Maul, Tim, 281743 (Box 22)
  - Menszer, 281742 (Box 22)
  - Martin, Daria, 281741 (Box 22)
  - Maslov, 281740 (Box 22)
  - Matheson, Elizabeth, 281739 (Box 22)
  - Mattison, Harry, 281738 (Box 22)
  - Mauskopf, Norman, 281737 (Box 22)
  - Mays, Elaine, 281736 (Box 22)
  - McAdams, Dona Ann, 281735 (Box 22)
  - McClintock, Lesley, 281734 (Box 22)
  - McCormack, Forrest, 281733 (Box 22)
  - McCormick, Chandra, 281732 (Box 22)
  - McCourt, Everett, 281731 (Box 22)
  - McDonald, Anne Arden, 281730 (Box 22)
  - McDonough, Paul, 281729 (Box 22)
  - McDowell, Bill, 281728 (Box 22)
  - McElroy, Michael, 281727 (Box 22)
  - McGowen, 281726 (Box 22)
  - McGregor, Merideth, 281725 (Box 22)
  - McGovern, Tom, 281724 (Box 23)
  - McGuirk, Paul, 281723 (Box 23)
  - McKenna, Rollie, 281722 (Box 23)
  - McKibben, Bill, 281721 (Box 23)
  - McLain, David, 281720 (Box 23)
  - McLean, Patricia, 281719 (Box 23)
  - McMahon, Conette, 281718 (Box 23)
  - McNair, Giles, 281717 (Box 23)
  - McPherson, Larry, 281716 (Box 23)
  - McPhillips, Ramsey, 281715 (Box 23)
  - McWilliams, John, 281714 (Box 23)
  - Meiselas, Susan, 281713 (Box 23)
  - Mendoza, Tony, 281712 (Box 23)
  - Mermelstein, Jeff, 281711 (Box 23)
  - Merritt, Sandra, 281710 (Box 23)
  - Messina, Elizabeth, 281709 (Box 23)
  - Meyer, Kurt (with Pam Deuel), 281708 (Box 23)
  - Meyer, Pedro, 281707 (Box 23)
  - Meyerowitz, Joel (2 folders), 281706 (Box 23)
  - Meyer, Jeffrey, 281705 (Box 23)
  - Michahelles, Sandro, 281704 (Box 23)
  - Michaels, Duane, 281703 (Box 23)
  - Mieth, Hansel, 281702 (Box 23)
  - Milanowski, Stephen R., 281701 (Box 23)
  - Milisenda, John, 281700 (Box 23)
  - Miller, Brian, 281699 (Box 23)
  - Miller, Howard Seth, 281698 (Box 24)
  - Miller, John, 281697 (Box 24)
  - Miller, Ken, 281696 (Box 24)
  - Miller, Peter, APX, Inc., 281695 (Box 24)
  - Miller, Rex, 281694 (Box 24)
  - Miller, Sybil, 281693 (Box 24)
  - Miller, Van, 281692 (Box 24)
  - Miller, Wayne F., 281691 (Box 24)
  - Milnor, Daniel (2 folders), 281690 (Box 24)
  - Mintz, Brad, 281689 (Box 24)
  - Mircik, Laura, 281688 (Box 24)
  - Mirer, Daniel, 281687 (Box 24)
  - Misrach, Richard (2 folders), 281686 (Box 24)
  - Mississippi Self-Portrait, 281685 (Box 24)
  - Missbach, Leah, 281684 (Box 24)
  - Mitchel, Julio, 281683 (Box 24)
  - Miuccio, Liana, 281682 (Box 24)
  - Miyoshi, Kozo, 281681 (Box 24)
  - Modica, Andrea, 281680 (Box 24)
  - Mofokeng, Santu, 281679 (Box 24)
  - Molenhuis, Jacob, 281678 (Box 24)
  - Monastario, Pablo, 281677 (Box 24)
  - Monfort, Regina, 281676 (Box 24)
  - Montag, Daro, 281675 (Box 24)
  - Monroe, Gary (2 folders), 281674 (Box 24)
  - Montgomery, Scott, 281673 (Box 25)
  - Monroe, Peter, 281672 (Box 25)
  - Moody, Phil, 281671 (Box 25)
  - Moos, Viviane, 281670 (Box 25)
  - Moran, Nancy, 281669 (Box 25)
  - Morrell, Abe, 281668 (Box 25)
  - Morgenstern, Eve, 281667 (Box 25)
  - Moriarty, Brian, 281666 (Box 25)
  - Morphew, Lisa, 281665 (Box 25)
  - Morris, Chris, 281664 (Box 25)
  - Morris, David Rae, 281663 (Box 25)
  - Morton, Margaret, 281662 (Box 25)
  - Moser, Lida, 281661 (Box 25)
  - Moses, John, 281660 (Box 25)
  - Mosier, Phillip, 281659 (Box 25)
  - Mott, Michele, 281658 (Box 25)
  - Mueller, Laura, 281657 (Box 25)
  - Muhammad, Nzingah, 281656 (Box 25)
  - Mullaney, Peter, 281655 (Box 25)
  - Mullins, Pictureman, 281654 (Box 25)
  - Murray, Felicia, 281653 (Box 25)
  - Murray, Katie, 281652 (Box 25)
  - Myers, Art, 281651 (Box 25)
  - Myers, Joan, 281650 (Box 25)
  - Nabokov, Dominique, 281649 (Box 25)
  - Nance, Marilyn, 281648 (Box 25)
  - NASA, 281647 (Box 25)
  - Neel, David, 281646 (Box 25)
  - Neff, Thomas, 281645 (Box 25)
  - Nelson, Erik, 281644 (Box 25)
  - Neto, Mario Cravo, 281643 (Box 25)
  - Neumann, William, 281642 (Box 25)
  - Nevel, Jocelyn, 281641 (Box 25)
  - Newton, Robert, 281640 (Box 25)
  - Nicol, James, 281639 (Box 25)
  - Nicoll, Link, 281638 (Box 25)
  - Nicosia, Nic, 281637 (Box 25)
  - Nisselson, Evan, 281636 (Box 25)
  - Nixon, Nicholas (2 folders), 281635 (Box 26)
  - Nobuyoshi, Fujiwara, 281634 (Box 26)
  - Noel, Laura Allen, 281633 (Box 26)
  - Noland, William, 281632 (Box 26)
  - Norfleet, Barbara, 281631 (Box 26)
  - Norris, Barry, 281630 (Box 26)
  - O'Connor, Flannery, 281629 (Box 26)
  - O'Connor, Rosalie, 281628 (Box 26)
  - Oglesbee, Brian, 281627 (Box 26)
  - Ogneov, Valentin, 281626 (Box 26)
  - O'Hare, Patrick, 281625 (Box 26)
  - Okun, Willy, 281624 (Box 26)
  - Ollman, Arthur, 281623 (Box 27)
  - Olmstead, Fredrick Law (2 folders), 281622 (Box 27)
  - Omenetto, Christine, 281621 (Box 27)
  - O'Neil, Nancy Kavanagh, 281620 (Box 27)
  - O'Neil, Robert Joseph, 281619 (Box 27)
  - Orkin, Ruth, 281618 (Box 27)
  - Orstadius, Martin, 281617 (Box 27)
  - Osinski, Christine, 281616 (Box 27)
  - Owens, Don, 281615 (Box 27)
  - Owings, Gregory, 281614 (Box 27)
  - Pachano, Peter, 281613 (Box 27)
  - Packer, George, 281612 (Box 27)
  - Padilla, Darcy, 281611 (Box 27)
  - Padilla, Jennifer, 281610 (Box 27)
  - Page, Susan, 281609 (Box 27)
  - Papageorge, Tod, 281608 (Box 28)
  - Pallotta, Lina, 281607 (Box 28)
  - Parada, Esther, 281606 (Box 28)
  - Parady, Judy, 281605 (Box 28)
  - Paresky, Laura, 281604 (Box 28)
  - Parker, Clare, 281603 (Box 28)
  - Parker, Michael, 281602 (Box 28)
  - Pastor, Nancy, 281601 (Box 28)
  - Parr, Martin, 281600 (Box 28)
  - Patrice, Susan, 281599 (Box 28)
  - Patterson, Neil, 281598 (Box 28)
  - Paul, Greg, 281597 (Box 28)
  - Peattie, Peggy, 281596 (Box 28)
  - Peck, Mary, 281595 (Box 28)
  - Pellegrin, Paolo, 281594 (Box 28)
  - Peress, Gilles (2 folders), 281593 (Box 28)
  - Perkis, Phil, 281592 (Box 28)
  - Perkins, James, 281591 (Box 28)
  - Perlman, Ilene, 281590 (Box 28)
  - Peters, Ed, 281589 (Box 28)
  - Peterson, Cheers Mark, 281588 (Box 28)
  - Petrenko, Anatoly, 281587 (Box 28)
  - Petroff, Paul, 281586 (Box 28)
  - Pfhal, John, 281585 (Box 28)
  - Pfontenhauer, Rachel, 281584 (Box 28)
  - Phillips, Jan, 281583 (Box 28)
  - Pierce, Olive, 281582 (Box 28)
  - Pillar, Heather, 281581 (Box 28)
  - Pilaro, Chris, 281580 (Box 28)
  - Pilson, John, 281579 (Box 28)
  - Pinckley, Donna, 281578 (Box 28)
  - Pinderhughes, John, 281577 (Box 28)
  - Pinkel, Sheila, 281576 (Box 28)
  - Pinney, Melissa Ann, 281575 (Box 28)
  - Pitts, Ves, 281574 (Box 28)
  - Plachy, Sylvia, 281573 (Box 29)
  - PoKempner, Marc, 281572 (Box 29)
  - Poli, Mariella, 281571 (Box 29)
  - Poniatowska, Elena, 281570 (Box 29)
  - Porter, Louise, 281569 (Box 29)
  - Post, Susan, 281568 (Box 29)
  - Post, Susie, 281567 (Box 29)
  - Postal, Johnathan, 281566 (Box 29)
  - Prager, Brenda, 281565 (Box 29)
  - Prancia, Steven, 281564 (Box 29)
  - Pratt, Charles, 281563 (Box 29)
  - Price, Daniel, 281562 (Box 29)
  - Pushinsky, Ted, 281561 (Box 29)
  - Putnum, Jesse Ward, 281560 (Box 29)
  - Putnam, Michael, 281559 (Box 29)
  - Quackenbush, Michael, 281558 (Box 29)
  - Raab, Michael, 281557 (Box 29)
  - Rabung, Mark, 281556 (Box 29)
  - Rachman, Barron, 281555 (Box 29)
  - Radin, Robin, 281554 (Box 29)
  - Rainier, Chris, 281553 (Box 29)
  - Ramirez, Joseph, 281552 (Box 29)
  - Ranard, John, 281551 (Box 29)
  - Randlett, Mary, 281550 (Box 29)
  - Randazzo, Joseph, 281549 (Box 29)
  - Rankin, Tom, 281548 (Box 29)
  - Ranney, Ed, 281547 (Box 29)
  - Rapport, Leonard, 281546 (Box 29)
  - Ratner, David, 281545 (Box 29)
  - Ravanesi, Bill, 281544 (Box 29)
  - Ravid, Joyce, 281543 (Box 29)
  - Ray, Gypsy, 281542 (Box 29)
  - Read, David, 281541 (Box 29)
  - Read, Tory, 281540 (Box 29)
  - Rechberger, Kristin, 281539 (Box 29)
  - Records, Shawn, 281538 (Box 29)
  - Reed, David, 281537 (Box 30)
  - Reed, Eli, 281536 (Box 30)
  - Reichert, Robert, 281535 (Box 30)
  - Reiff, Patricia, 281534 (Box 30)
  - Rein, Ilana, 281533 (Box 30)
  - Reiten, Julie, 281532 (Box 30)
  - Rembisz, Rick, 281531 (Box 30)
  - Rhodes, Marvin, 281530 (Box 30)
  - Rice, Tim, 281529 (Box 30)
  - Richards, Eugene, 281528 (Box 30)
  - Richardson, Doug, 281527 (Box 30)
  - Richardson, Nan, 281526 (Box 30)
  - Richman, Brad, 281525 (Box 30)
  - Richter, Curt, 281524 (Box 30)
  - Rieger, Sonja, 281523 (Box 30)
  - Riley, Chris, 281522 (Box 30)
  - Robbins, David, 281521 (Box 30)
  - Roberts, Ines E., 281520 (Box 30)
  - Robinson, Abby, 281519 (Box 30)
  - Robinson, David, 281518 (Box 30)
  - Roemer, Jon, 281517 (Box 30)
  - Rodriguez, Joe, 281516 (Box 30)
  - Rodrigues, Sebastian and Fran Antmann, 281515 (Box 30)
  - Roma, Tom (8 folders), 281514 (Box 30)
  - Rome, Stuart, 281513 (Box 31)
  - Rose, Alan (2 folders), 281512 (Box 31)
  - Rosen, Diana, 281511 (Box 31)
  - Rosenstein, Peter, 281510 (Box 31)
  - Rosenthal, Mel, 281509 (Box 31)
  - Ross, Judith, 281508 (Box 31)
  - Ross, Richard, 281507 (Box 31)
  - Rosser, Ed, 281506 (Box 31)
  - Rost, Yuri, 281505 (Box 31)
  - Rostagni, Jean-Christian, 281504 (Box 31)
  - Roster, Tom, 281503 (Box 31)
  - Roth, Marissa, 281502 (Box 31)
  - Rothenberg, Daniel, 281501 (Box 31)
  - Rothman, Richard, 281500 (Box 31)
  - Rouda, Bill, 281499 (Box 31)
  - Rupp, Sheron, 281498 (Box 31)
  - Rubenstein, Meridel, 281497 (Box 32)
  - Ruben, Steven, 281496 (Box 32)
  - Rusten, Shelly, 281495 (Box 32)
  - Ryerson, Marjorie, 281494 (Box 32)
  - Rynne, M.K., 281493 (Box 32)
  - Saah, Jim, 281492 (Box 32)
  - Sacha, Bob, 281491 (Box 32)
  - Sager, 281490 (Box 32)
  - Saitta, Giuseppe, 281489 (Box 32)
  - Salguereo, Carolina, 281488 (Box 32)
  - Salinger, Adrienne, 281487 (Box 32)
  - Salter, Jeffery Allan, 281486 (Box 32)
  - Salvador, Cristina, 281485 (Box 32)
  - Salvo, Dana, 281484 (Box 32)
  - Salzmann, Lawrence, 281483 (Box 32)
  - Sanders, Kim, 281482 (Box 32)
  - Sandoval, George, 281481 (Box 32)
  - Sandoval, Judith H., 281480 (Box 32)
  - Sartor, Margaret (2 folders), 281479 (Box 32)
  - Saville, Lynn, 281478 (Box 32)
  - Savulich, Andrew, 281477 (Box 32)
  - Scales, Jeffery Henson, 281476 (Box 32)
  - Scans, 281475 (Box 32)
  - Schaefer, Linda, 281474 (Box 32)
  - Schatz, Howard, 281473 (Box 32)
  - Scheer, Bill, 281472 (Box 32)
  - Schendler, Virginia, 281471 (Box 32)
  - Schles, Ken, 281470 (Box 32)
  - Schmelling, Michael, 281469 (Box 32)
  - Schmidt, Bastienne, 281468 (Box 33)
  - Schmidt, Joachim, 281467 (Box 33)
  - Schreibman, Jane, 281466 (Box 33)
  - Schultz, Barbara, 281465 (Box 33)
  - Schwartz, Janet, 281464 (Box 33)
  - Schwartz, Jason, 281463 (Box 33)
  - Schwartz, Robin, 281462 (Box 33)
  - Schwartz, Staci, 281461 (Box 33)
  - Schwartzreich, Paul, 281460 (Box 33)
  - Scorsese, Martin, 281459 (Box 33)
  - Scott, Allison, 281458 (Box 33)
  - Scott, Anderson, 281457 (Box 33)
  - Scruton, Fred, 281456 (Box 33)
  - Seding, Volker, 281455 (Box 33)
  - Seeing the Elephant (Shawn Aubitz), 281454 (Box 33)
  - Segal, Gregg, 281453 (Box 33)
  - Seif, Bob, 281452 (Box 33)
  - Sekaer, Peter, 281451 (Box 34)
  - Serotta, Edward, 281450 (Box 34)
  - Sgroi, Fabio, 281449 (Box 34)
  - Shafren, Nigel, 281448 (Box 34)
  - Shamblin, Barbara, 281447 (Box 34)
  - Shambroom, Paul, 281446 (Box 34)
  - Sheikh, Fazal, 281445 (Box 34)
  - Shemper, Adam, 281444 (Box 34)
  - Short, William and Willia Seidenberg, 281443 (Box 34)
  - Shames, Steven, 281442 (Box 34)
  - Shamis, Bob, 281441 (Box 34)
  - Shapiro, Toni, 281440 (Box 34)
  - Sharlin, Johnathan, 281439 (Box 34)
  - Sharp, Trish, 281438 (Box 34)
  - Sherbell, Shepard, 281437 (Box 34)
  - Shirer, Stan, 281436 (Box 34)
  - Sherman, Ken, 281435 (Box 34)
  - Shifrin, Jean, 281434 (Box 34)
  - Shimon, John and Julie Lindermann, 281433 (Box 34)
  - Shook, Melissa, 281432 (Box 34)
  - Shore, Stephen, 281431 (Box 34)
  - Silberman, Robert, 281430 (Box 34)
  - Silberman, Zia, 281429 (Box 34)
  - Silbert, Layle, 281428 (Box 34)
  - Sills, Vaughn (2 folders), 281427 (Box 34)
  - Simone, Chip, 281426 (Box 34)
  - Sindler, Mark, 281425 (Box 34)
  - Singh, Dayanita, 281424 (Box 34)
  - Singh, Raghubir, 281423 (Box 34)
  - Sira, Victor, 281422 (Box 35)
  - Siskind, Lawrence, 281421 (Box 35)
  - Sixth Street Photog Workshop (Maggie Perkins), 281420 (Box 35)
  - Sklar, Evan, 281419 (Box 35)
  - Slavin, Neil, 281418 (Box 35)
  - Sligh, Clarissa, 281417 (Box 35)
  - Slesnick, Les, 281416 (Box 35)
  - Sloan, John, 281415 (Box 35)
  - Smith, Brad A., 281414 (Box 35)
  - Smith, D. K., 281413 (Box 35)
  - Smith, Lindy, 281412 (Box 35)
  - Smith, Maggie, 281411 (Box 35)
  - Smith, Steve, 281410 (Box 35)
  - Smith, W. Eugene (2 folders), 281409 (Box 35)
  - Smogor, Linda, 281408 (Box 35)
  - Snider, David, 281407 (Box 35)
  - Solomon, Rosalind, 281406 (Box 35)
  - Spano, Michael, 281405 (Box 35)
  - Spear, David, 281404 (Box 35)
  - Spears, Ross, 281403 (Box 35)
  - Spiegel, Marjorie, 281402 (Box 35)
  - Spragg, Stacia, 281401 (Box 35)
  - Springsteen, Pamela, 281400 (Box 35)
  - Spuntoff, Richard, 281399 (Box 35)
  - Staller, Jan, 281398 (Box 35)
  - Stamets, John, 281397 (Box 35)
  - Stanton, C. E., 281396 (Box 35)
  - Stava, Susan, 281395 (Box 35)
  - Stearn, Peter, 281394 (Box 35)
  - Steber, Maggie, 281393 (Box 35)
  - Steensma, Jennifer, 281392 (Box 35)
  - Stein, Harvey, 281391 (Box 35)
  - Steinmetz, Mark, 281390 (Box 35)
  - Stern, Andrea, 281389 (Box 35)
  - Sternfeld, Joel (2 folders), 281388 (Box 35)
  - Stewart, Sharon, 281387 (Box 36)
  - Stilley, Ricky, 281386 (Box 36)
  - Stock, David, 281385 (Box 36)
  - Stone, Jim, 281384 (Box 36)
  - Stone, Les, 281383 (Box 36)
  - Stovall, Julie, 281382 (Box 36)
  - Stratton, Margaret, 281381 (Box 36)